I got you covered.
Just relax.
Take it easy.
Take it easy. Calm down.
Stay with me.
- Stay with me.
- Okay, okay.
Give me some.
Okay.
We're moving you
to another hospital, all right?
Oh.
Hello?!
Hey!
Anyone?!
Hello?
Hello?!
Yeah.
Hello?
Can anybody hear me?
If anybody's out there,
if anybody can hear my voice,
my name is Ben Neilson, and
I'm in an ambulance on a road,
and there's nobody here.
And... I'm blind.
I can't see.
Oh!
Aah.
Hey!
Aah! Aah!
Oh!
Run. Run.
Please enter your password.
You have one saved
wireless voice message.
- First saved message.
- Hi, honey. It's Mom.
Just wanted to wish you
a good last day at work
and to let you know
I don't think
we can make it down
to see you tomorrow.
Dad really isn't feeling well.
Okay, love you.
Bye.
Hello? Hello?
If anybody can hear my
voice, my name is Ben Neilson,
and I'm in an ambulance...
Hello? Do you read me?
...on a road,
and there's nobody here.
Hello.
This is Officer Mara Madigan.
I'm not sure
if anyone can hear this.
My walkie's acting up.
I'm headed into the station now.
Wait! Wait!
Miss, is everything okay?
This is Officer Madigan.
I have a situation
out here on Grey Route 40.
Stay back!
Aah!
I can take you to a hospital.
I'm gonna get you a blanket.
I'm so sorry.
I'm sorry.
- I'm so sorry.
- Okay.
You're okay.
I've called for help.
They're on their way.
You're gonna be okay.
I'm sorry.
Miss.
Hey. Hello?!
Anyone?
Hello?
Anybody?
1...
2...
3...
4...
5, 6, 7...
8, 9, 10, 11.
Table, chair.
11, 12...
13, 14, 15...
16, 17...
18. Right.
Steps, stairs.
12, 13, 14.
20...
21...
22...
Aah!
No! No!
No!
Oh! Oh!
Aah! Aah!
Hey!
Please. Please!
Stay right there!
Help me.
- Please, I can't see.
- Are you sick?
- What?
- No.
- Do you live here?
No.
I don't know where I am.
I don't know how I got here.
Please.
I'm Officer Mara Madigan.
We're in a farmhouse
just outside of town.
Did she hurt you?
No.
You're a police officer?
Please.
I'm not sick.
My name is Ben.
Ben what?
Ben Neilson.
Oh!
Thank God.
What the fuck is this?
I need to secure the house.
No. No. Please.
Please, don't...
You can't leave me here.
- Please!
- Sit down!
Are you hurt?
No.
Where are we going?
I'm taking you to the cellar.
- Why?
- Come on.
- Tell me why.
- It's safer down there.
Can you uncuff me?
No.
What are you having?
What?
My wife, when she was pregnant
with our daughter...
...she got really fat.
She got as big as a house,
and she was out of breath
all the time...
when she stood up, sat down,
turned around, bent over,
when she
did pretty much anything.
I think it's a boy.
We can't stay.
You need to rest.
How did you get here?
I don't remember.
I woke up in the middle of
nowhere, back of an ambulance.
Everybody was gone.
They were transferring me
'cause of, uh...
I tried using the radio,
but there's nobody out there.
- This morning?
- Yeah.
I heard you.
On the radio.
That was you.
You did?
Okay.
Ben, we need to get
to that ambulance.
No.
No, it's
It's not safe out there.
It's not safe here.
I have a gun.
If you made it here,
then we can make it there.
Someone shot at me on the road.
Well, they're not gonna
shoot you this time.
Stay right with me, okay?
Hand on my shoulder.
And don't talk.
- Get down!
- What?! What?!
Mara?
Are you okay?
I'm fine.
Oh, fuck.
You can't come with me.
What?
I've got two bullets left.
It's gonna be dark soon.
Mara, you won't survive.
Two bullets is not enough.
I won't survive with you.
Hello?
I don't know
if anyone can hear this.
But this is
Officer Mara Madigan.
I'm in a farmhouse
on Grey Route 19.
There is a man named Ben Neilson
in the basement.
He's blind and wounded,
but he's informed me that
there is an ambulance somewhere.
So I'm gonna go find it
and come back for him.
In case something happens
to me...
...please, someone come get him.
Over and out.
It's me.
- Where'd you go?
- I got you an ax.
- An ax?
- Yeah.
Jesus Christ.
And... this.
Wait.
What's this for?
Okay, it leads to the back door.
I'm gonna go find the ambulance
and bring it back here.
Lock the door behind me.
I shouldn't be
more than an hour.
I-I really think
we should stay together.
If something gets in,
use the ax,
follow the rope, and run.
Where?
Out the back.
I'll meet you in the woods.
Fuck.
Hey.
I'll find you.
Mara?
No. Oh, no!
Oh, come on.
Hello?
No!
No.
Hello? Anyone?
"Ben Neilson.
House fire.
Suspect in custody
for suspicious deaths...
one child, one adult.
Possibly suicidal."
Oh.
Hello?
Hello?!
Hey!
Huh?
Hello?
Here.
No.
It's for the shoulder.
Right.
Thought you were one of them.
No hard feelings.
Yeah.
- Hey, you were on the road.
- Yeah.
Thought we already killed you.
So did I.
You keep shooting at me.
That was my cousin Harlan.
I'm the better shot.
Where is he?
He's gone.
You a doctor?
Mnh-mnh.
No.
You look like a doctor.
No, I'm not a doctor.
Take it.
It's loaded.
What am I supposed to do
with it?
You're gonna shoot me with it.
What?
I said, "You're gonna
shoot me with it."
No, I'm not.
Well, you're gonna have to.
Or what?
I saw what they did to Harlan.
What are you?
Are you a coward?
Yeah.
I am.
Why don't
you just do it yourself?
I couldn't do it.
So I'm gonna sit here
and keep talking...
...so you can know
where to aim when you're ready.
We thought we were ready.
Thought we were ready for this.
Harlan was talking
about a program.
A broadcast he heard
about the flu shot mutating.
So
I thought I'd be all right.
'Cause I didn't get one.
Aah!
Fuck!
Ben?!
Ben!
Aah! Aah!
Shit.
Oh! No!
- Mara?
- Ben!
- Mara!
- Ben, I'm over here!
- Mara, are you okay?
- Yeah.
- Did I hit you?
- No.
Are you all right?
I thought I lost you.
Not yet.
We got to get out of here.
- I'm okay.
- You okay?
Yeah, I got to sit down.
Where's the ambulance?
It's dead.
You left it running.
Fuck.
I found something.
What?
Oh! Oh!
Are you having contractions?
No.
I think it's just the stress.
Has anything stressful
happened to you recently?
Okay.
I'm having a contraction.
Come on.
Let's go.
It's all right.
Come on.
Come on, come on, come on.
That's it.
- Oh, there's the door.
- Okay.
Come on.
Okay.
All right.
Rest here a second.
Come on.
There you go.
Go slow.
Go slow. Go slow.
Oh!
- Here.
- Oh!
Okay. All right.
Okay.
It's too early.
Ohh!
- It's too early.
- Just...
...relax.
Just breathe.
The baby's gonna come.
No. No.
You got another few hours yet.
Just breathe.
Breathe.
2.
3.
4.
Ben.
They're inside.
- We have to go.
- The door is locked.
- We're safe in here.
- No, no, no.
Mara, if you have that baby
in here, you'll both die.
I can't move.
You have to.
We're not gonna make it.
We have to fight our way out.
Listen.
You be my eyes.
I'll get you outside.
Go.
Come on.
1. 2. 2 shots.
We have to reload.
Come on.
Aah!
Mara, run!
Hey. Hey.
Hey.
We got to go.
Come on.
All right.
No!
All right. Come on.
Come on.
Almost there.